Political Research Associates Records MS014
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Publications, 1908 -- 2011; MS014.001; 91.2 Linear Feet
  - Trotter Institute Review, 1987; MS014.001.071.00006; William Monroe Trotter Institute (Box 71)
  - The Trumpet, 1993 -- 1998; MS014.001.071.00007; Collegians Activated to Liberate Life (Box 71)
  - Trustees for Better Teachers, 2005; MS014.001.071.00008; American Council of Trustees and Alumni (Box 71)
  - Truth & Triumph, 2008; MS014.001.071.00009; Alliance Defense Fund (Box 71)
  - The Truth at Last [1 of 4], 1988; MS014.001.071.00010; Thunderbolt, Inc. (Box 71)
  - The Truth at Last [2 of 4], 1988; MS014.001.071.00011; Thunderbolt, Inc. (Box 71)
  - The Truth at Last [3 of 4], 1988; MS014.001.071.00012; Thunderbolt, Inc. (Box 71)
  - The Truth at Last [4 of 4], 1988; MS014.001.071.00013; Thunderbolt, Inc. (Box 71)
  - The Truth Crusader, 1970; MS014.001.071.00014; Miller, Ernest L. and Mary G. Miller (Box 71)
  - Truth Forum, 1970 -- 1971; MS014.001.071.00015 (Box 71)
  - Tundra Drums, The, 1990; MS014.001.071.00016; The Drums (Box 71)
  - Turn the Hearts, 1992; MS014.001.071.00017; California Coalition for Life (Box 71)
  - TV, etc., 1990 -- 1995; MS014.001.071.00018; Media Research Center (Box 71)
  - Individual "T" Articles, MS014.001.071.00019 (Box 71)
  - UAW Washington Report, 1986; MS014.001.071.00020; United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (Box 71)
  - UB Newsletter, 1994; MS014.001.071.00021; Church of the United Brethren in Christ (Box 71)
  - UFO, 1992; MS014.001.071.00022; California UFO (Box 71)
  - UFO Investigator, 1972 -- 1973; MS014.001.071.00023; National Investigations Committee on Aerial Phenomena, Inc. (Box 71)
  - UFO Magazine, 2000; MS014.001.071.00024 (Box 71)
  - Ukranian Echo, 1990 -- 1992; MS014.001.071.00025; Homin Ukrainy (Box 71)
  - Ukranian Orthodox Word, 1991 -- 1992; MS014.001.071.00026 (Box 71)
  - Ulster, 1990; MS014.001.071.00027; Ulster Information Service (Box 71)
  - Ulster Commentary, 1979; MS014.001.071.00028; Northern Ireland Government Information Service (Box 71)
  - Ultimate Issues, 1992 -- 1996; MS014.001.071.00029; Prager, Dennis (Box 71)
  - Ultimatum, MS014.001.071.00030 (Box 71)
  - Unclassified, 1995; MS014.001.071.00031; Association of National Security Alumni (Box 71)
  - Under Attack from the Far-Right, Public Workers, Public Services, MS014.001.071.00032 (Box 71)
  - Unification News, 2001 -- 2003; MS014.001.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - The Union Advocate, 1998; MS014.001.072.00002 (Box 72)
  - Union Update, 2001; MS014.001.072.00003; Public Service Alliance of Canada (Box 72)
  - Unionism, 1973; MS014.001.072.00004; United states National Student Association (Box 72)
  - Unitarian Universalist Association General Assembly, 1999; MS014.001.072.00005; Unitarian Universalist Association (Box 72)
  - Unite!, 1998; MS014.001.072.00006; Union of Needletrades, Industrial & Textile Employees, AFL-CIO, CLC (Box 72)
  - Unite!, 1981; MS014.001.072.00007; Tyler, Gary (Box 72)
  - Unite!, 1982; MS014.001.072.00008; Communist Party U.S.A/Marxist-Leninist (Box 72)
  - United States Institute of Peace Journal, 1992 -- 1994; MS014.001.072.00009; United States Institute of Peace (Box 72)
  - The University Bookman, 1982 -- 1995; MS014.001.072.00010; The Educational Reviewer, Inc. (Box 72)
  - The University News, 1982; MS014.001.072.00011 (Box 72)
  - The University of Denver Magazine, 2001 -- 2010; MS014.001.072.00012; The University of Denver (Box 72)
  - Unpacking Globalization, 2000; MS014.001.072.00013; Economic Literacy Action Network (Box 72)
  - Unravelling the New World Order, 2001 -- 2004; MS014.001.072.00014; FAMC, Inc. (Box 72)
  - Uplink, 1996; MS014.001.072.00015; National Institute for Computer-Assisted Reporting (Box 72)
  - UpMagazine, MS014.001.072.00016 (Box 72)
  - URI Update, 2004; MS014.001.072.00017; United Religions Initiative (Box 72)
  - U.S. PIRG Citizen Agenda, 1997 -- 2007; MS014.001.072.00018; U.S. Public Interest Research Group (Box 72)
  - U.S./Labor Education in the Americas Project, 2001; MS014.001.072.00019 (Box 72)
  - U.S.A., 1977; MS014.001.072.00020; U.S.A. Publishing Company, Inc. (Box 72)
  - USA Next, 2004 -- 2005; MS014.001.072.00021; United Seniors Association and USA Next (Box 72)
  - THE USNSA Life Insurance Trust, MS014.001.072.00022; United states National Student Association (Box 72)
  - Valkyrie, 1994; MS014.001.072.00023 (Box 72)
  - Values, 1970; MS014.001.072.00024 (Box 72)
  - Values Voter Summit, 2009; MS014.001.072.00025; Family Research Council (Box 72)
  - Vanguard, 1990; MS014.001.072.00026; Vanguard Publications (Box 72)
  - Verdict, 2006; MS014.001.072.00027; National Coalition of Concerned Legal Professionals (Box 72)
  - Veritas, 1992; MS014.001.072.00028 (Box 72)
  - Veritas Report, 1975; MS014.001.072.00029; Veritas Foundation (Box 72)
  - Veritas Vincit, 1997 -- 1998; MS014.001.072.00030; Trinity International University (Box 72)
  - The Veteran, 1998 -- 2010; MS014.001.072.00031; Vietnam Veterans of America (Box 72)
  - The Vigil Newsletter, 1985; MS014.001.072.00032; Des Plaines Pro Life - "The Prayer People" (Box 72)
  - Virginia Christian Israelite, 1996; MS014.001.072.00033; Virginia Christian Israelites (Box 72)
  - The Virginia Citizen, 1997; MS014.001.072.00034; The Family Foundation (Box 72)
  - Virtue, Christian Magazine for Women, 1991 -- 2000; MS014.001.072.00035; Virtue Magazine (Box 72)
  - Vision and Values, 1993 -- 2000; MS014.001.072.00036; Grove City College Alumni Association (Box 72)
  - Vista, 1996 -- 2002; MS014.001.072.00037; Radio for Peace International (Box 72)
  - Vita Wa Watu, 1988; MS014.001.072.00038; Spear and Shield Publications (Box 72)
  - Voces Unidas, 1996 -- 2009; MS014.001.072.00039; SouthWest Organizing Project (Box 72)
  - Voice, 1997 -- 1999; MS014.001.072.00040; Of the People Foundation (Box 72)
  - The Voice in the Wilderness, 1993; MS014.001.072.00041; Voice in the Wilderness (Box 72)
  - Voice of Liberty, 1988 -- 1991; MS014.001.072.00042; The Voice of Liberty Association (Box 72)
  - Voice of Reason, 1990 -- 2010; MS014.001.072.00043; American Humanist Association (Box 72)
  - The Voice of the Martyrs, 1999 -- 2008; MS014.001.073.00001; The Voice of the Martyrs, Inc. (Box 73)
  - Voice of the People, 1995 -- 1997; MS014.001.073.00002; Of the People Foundation (Box 73)
  - Voices for the Unborn, 1993 -- 1996; MS014.001.073.00003; Feasterville, PA (Box 73)
  - Voices from the Earth, 2007 -- 2009; MS014.001.073.00004; Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 73)
  - Voting Records, 1996; MS014.001.073.00005; BIPAC (Box 73)
  - Voting with a Clear Conscience, 2006; MS014.001.073.00006; Priests for Life (Box 73)
  - La Voz de Esperanza, 2004; MS014.001.073.00007; Esperanza Peace & Justice Center (Box 73)
  - Individual "V" Articles, MS014.001.073.00008 (Box 73)
  - Wake Up!, 1991 -- 1993; MS014.001.073.00009; Kingdom Foundation (Box 73)
  - Wake-up Call America, 1995 -- 1996; MS014.001.073.00010 (Box 73)
  - Walk Away, 1994; MS014.001.073.00011; Institute for First Amendment Studies (Box 73)
  - The WallBuilder Report, 1993 -- 2002; MS014.001.073.00012; WallBuilders, Inc. (Box 73)
  - WAR [1 of 3], 1985 -- 1993; MS014.001.073.00013; White Aryan Resistance (Box 73)
  - WAR [2 of 3], 1987 -- 1993; MS014.001.073.00014; White Aryan Resistance (Box 73)
  - WAR [3 of 3], 1985 -- 1995; MS014.001.073.00015; White Aryan Resistance (Box 73)
  - War and Peace Digest, 1991 -- 1997; MS014.001.073.00016; War & Peace Foundation (Box 73)
  - War Cry, 2001; MS014.001.073.00017; The Salvation Army (Box 73)
  - The War Eagle, 1993; MS014.001.073.00018 (Box 73)
  - The War is Now!, 1990; MS014.001.073.00019; Australian Alliance for Catholic Tradition (Box 73)
  - War Research Info Service, 1985 -- 1992; MS014.001.073.00020; University Conversion Project (Box 73)
  - War Times [1 of 2], 2002 -- 2004; MS014.001.073.00021; War Times (Box 73)
  - War Times [2 of 2], 2003; MS014.001.073.00022; War Times (Box 73)
  - Washington Briefing, 2006; MS014.001.073.00023; Values Voter Summit (Box 73)
  - Washington Citizen, 1997; MS014.001.073.00024; Washington Family Council (Box 73)
  - Washington City Paper, 1993; MS014.001.073.00025; Washington Free Weekly, Inc. (Box 73)
  - Washington Digest, 1987; MS014.001.073.00026; National Associatioin of Criminal Defense Lawyers (Box 73)
  - Washington Education Report, 1991; MS014.001.073.00027; LaHaye, Tim (Box 73)
  - Washington Inquirer [1 of 9], 1995 -- 1996; MS014.001.074.00001; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [2 of 9], 1996 -- 1997; MS014.001.074.00002; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [3 of 9], 1997 -- 1998; MS014.001.074.00003; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [4 of 9], 1997 -- 1999; MS014.001.074.00004; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [5 of 9], 1994 -- 1996; MS014.001.074.00005; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [6 of 9], 1994; MS014.001.074.00006; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [7 of 9], 1993 -- 1994; MS014.001.074.00007; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [8 of 9], 1992 -- 1993; MS014.001.074.00008; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Inquirer [9 of 9], 1990 -- 1992; MS014.001.074.00009; The Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 74)
  - Washington Intelligence Report, 1973; MS014.001.074.00010; US Anti-Communist Congress, Inc. (Box 74)
  - Washington Memo, 1982 -- 1985; MS014.001.074.00011; Alan Guttmacher Institute (Box 74)
  - Washington Peace Letter, 2004; MS014.001.074.00012; Washington Peace Center (Box 74)
  - Washington Report, 1977 -- 1994; MS014.001.074.00013; American Security Council Foundation (Box 74)
  - Washington State Watchman, 1996; MS014.001.074.00014; Christian Coalition of Washington (Box 74)
  - Washington Tribune, 1981; MS014.001.074.00015 (Box 74)
  - Washington Watch [1 of 3], 1995 -- 2000; MS014.001.074.00016; Family Research Council (Box 74)
  - Washington Watch [2 of 3], 1998 -- 2007; MS014.001.075.00001; Family Research Council (Box 75)
  - Washington Watch [3 of 3], 1994 -- 1998; MS014.001.075.00002; Family Research Council (Box 75)
  - Washington Weekly, 1979; MS014.001.075.00003 (Box 75)
  - Watch on the Right, 1981 -- 1983; MS014.001.075.00004; Iowa Freedom Foundatoin (Box 75)
  - The Watchdog, 2007 -- 2011; MS014.001.075.00005; Media Research Center (Box 75)
  - The Watchman Expositor, 2001; MS014.001.075.00006; Watchman Fellowship (Box 75)
  - The Watchtower, 1998 -- 2008; MS014.001.075.00007 (Box 75)
  - Watergate, MS014.001.075.00008; National Archives (Box 75)
  - Waves, 2004; MS014.001.075.00009; The Women's Project (Box 75)
  - Way Newsletter, 1987 -- 2001; MS014.001.075.00010; Church of Jesus Christ-Christian (Box 75)
  - WBAI Folio, 2003; MS014.001.075.00011; WBAI Radio (Box 75)
  - Weekend, MS014.001.075.00012 (Box 75)
  - Weep for Your Children, MS014.001.075.00013; Valley Christian University (Box 75)
  - West Watch, 1989 -- 1991; MS014.001.075.00014; Council for Inter-American Security (Box 75)
  - West Watch, 1977 -- 1989; MS014.001.075.00015; Council for Inter-American Security (Box 75)
  - Western Goals Report, 1981 -- 1985; MS014.001.075.00016; Western Goals (Box 75)
  - Western Horizons, 1993; MS014.001.075.00017; Wise Use Public Exposure Project (Box 75)
  - Western Review Institute Newsletter, 1992 -- 1993; MS014.001.075.00018; Western Review Institute (Box 75)
  - Western States Center, 1989 -- 1998; MS014.001.075.00019 (Box 75)
  - Western States Center, 1998 -- 2007; MS014.001.075.00020 (Box 75)
  - WGNRR, 2007; MS014.001.075.00021; Womens Global Network for Reproductive Rights (Box 75)
  - What They're Saying About Young Americans for Freedom, 1973; MS014.001.075.00022; Young Americans for Freedom (Box 75)
  - What You Should Know About Rhode Island's Durable Power of Attourney for Health Care, 1987; MS014.001.075.00023; The Human Life Center (Box 75)
  - When You Were Formed in Secret, 1984; MS014.001.075.00024; National Right to Life (Box 75)
  - Which Way Forward for the Anti Klan Movement, MS014.001.075.00025; Revolutionary Socialist League (Box 75)
  - The Whistleblower, 1990; MS014.001.075.00026 (Box 75)
  - Whistleblower [1 of 2], 2001 -- 2002; MS014.001.075.00027; worldnetdaily.com (Box 75)
  - Whistleblower [2 of 2], 2002 -- 2003; MS014.001.075.00028; worldnetdaily.com (Box 75)
  - The White American, 1965; MS014.001.075.00029 (Box 75)
  - White Beret, 1993; MS014.001.075.00030; White Knights of the KKK (Box 75)
  - White Patriot [1 of 2], 1985 -- 2001; MS014.001.075.00031; The Knights's Party of the KKK (Box 75)
  - White Patriot [2 of 2], MS014.001.075.00032; The Knights's Party of the KKK (Box 75)
  - White Power [1 of 2], 1974 -- 1979; MS014.001.076.00001; National Socialist White People's Party (Box 76)
  - White Power [2 of 2], 1978 -- 1981; MS014.001.076.00002; National Socialist White People's Party (Box 76)
  - White Sisters, 1991; MS014.001.076.00003; Aryan Womens League (Box 76)
  - White Wing Messenger, 1996; MS014.001.076.00004; Church of God of Prophecy (Box 76)
  - Whitewater News, 1994; MS014.001.076.00005 (Box 76)
  - Who Cares, 1999; MS014.001.076.00006 (Box 76)
  - Why You Can't Trust the News, 2003; MS014.001.076.00007; Accuracy in Media (Box 76)
  - Wilcox Report Newsletter, 1986 -- 1989; MS014.001.076.00008; Wilcox, Laird (Box 76)
  - Win Magazine, 1976 -- 1981; MS014.001.076.00009; W.I.N. Magazine, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Window on the Future, 1986; MS014.001.076.00010; National Right to Life Committee, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Wisconsin Conference Life, 1999; MS014.001.076.00011; United Church of Christ (Box 76)
  - Wisconsin Right to Life, 1991 -- 1994; MS014.001.076.00012; National Right to Life Committee, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Wisconsin Report, 1978 -- 1979; MS014.001.076.00013; Wisconsin Report Publishing Company, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Wisconsin Research Center for Pluralism Report, 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.076.00014; Wisconsin Research Center for Pluralism, Inc. (Box 76)
  - The Wisconsin Review, 1996; MS014.001.076.00015; The Common Sense Forum, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Wisconsin Update, 1991 -- 2001; MS014.001.076.00016; Wisconsin Policy Research Institute, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Witherspoon Fellowship Lectures, 2003; MS014.001.076.00017; Family Research Council (Box 76)
  - The Witness, 1990; MS014.001.076.00018; Dickinson, Curtis (Box 76)
  - The Woman Constitutionalist, 1981 -- 1985; MS014.001.076.00019; Women for Constitutional Government (Box 76)
  - Women Against Military Madness (WAMM), 1994 -- 1996; MS014.001.076.00020; Women Against Military Madness (Box 76)
  - Women on Campus, 1973; MS014.001.076.00021; United states National Student Association (Box 76)
  - Women's Foundation of Southern Arizona, 2005; MS014.001.076.00022; Community Foundation for Southern Arizona (Box 76)
  - Women's Institute News, 2005; MS014.001.076.00023; The Women's Institute (Box 76)
  - Women's Political Times, 2002 -- 2005; MS014.001.076.00024; National Women's Political Caucus (Box 76)
  - The Women's Union, 2005; MS014.001.076.00025 (Box 76)
  - The Word, 1992; MS014.001.076.00026; The Word Foundation, Inc. (Box 76)
  - Words of the Spirit, 1997; MS014.001.076.00027 (Box 76)
  - The Workbook, 1984 -- 1994; MS014.001.076.00028; Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 76)
  - The Workbook, 1983 -- 1990; MS014.001.076.00029; Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 76)
  - Workers Vanguard, 1995; MS014.001.076.00030; Spartacist League of the U.S. (Box 76)
  - Working for Free Enterprise, MS014.001.076.00031; ACU Education and Research Institute (Box 76)
  - Works in Progress, 1994 -- 1996; MS014.001.076.00032; Applied Research Center (Box 76)
  - World Alert, 1993; MS014.001.076.00033; Justice & Peace Center (Box 76)
  - World Changer! Newsletter, MS014.001.076.00034; World Changer! (Box 76)
  - World Christian, 1994; MS014.001.076.00035; World Christian, Inc. (Box 76)
  - World Congress of Families II & III, 1999 -- 2004; MS014.001.076.00036; Howard Center for Family, Religion & Society (Box 76)
  - World Domination Review, 1993 -- 1995; MS014.001.076.00037 (Box 76)
  - World Economic Review, 1986 -- 1987; MS014.001.076.00038; The World Economic Review (Box 76)
  - World Jewish Congress Report, 2006; MS014.001.076.00039; World Jewish Congress (Box 76)
  - World News Digest, 1993; MS014.001.076.00040; Soundview Publications, Inc. (Box 76)
  - WorldNet, 2000 -- 2001; MS014.001.076.00041; worldnetdaily.com (Box 76)
  - World University Times/World Student Times [1 of 4], 1983; MS014.001.077.00001; CARP (Box 77)
  - World University Times/World Student Times [2 of 4], 1985 -- 1987; MS014.001.077.00002; CARP (Box 77)
  - World University Times/World Student Times [3 of 4], 1984 -- 1985; MS014.001.077.00003; CARP (Box 77)
  - World University Times/World Student Times [4 of 4], 1982; MS014.001.077.00004; CARP (Box 77)
  - X-Poz, 1996; MS014.001.077.00005; Pennsylvania Expose (Box 77)
  - The Yankee Radical, 2000 -- 2010; MS014.001.077.00006; Democratic Socialists of America (Box 77)
  - Yes! [1 of 2], 2007 -- 2008; MS014.001.077.00007; Positive Futures Network (Box 77)
  - Yes! [2 of 2], 2008 -- 2010; MS014.001.077.00008; Positive Futures Network (Box 77)
  - Young People and Cults, 1986 -- 1992; MS014.001.077.00009; International Cult Education Program (Box 77)
  - Your Guide to Foreign Missions, 1990 -- 1991; MS014.001.077.00010; Southern Baptist Convention (Box 77)
  - Youth, 1990 -- 1994; MS014.001.077.00011; Worldwide Church of God (Box 77)
  - You've a Right to Know, 1977; MS014.001.077.00012; Rarick, John R. (Box 77)
  - Individual "Y" Articles, MS014.001.077.00013 (Box 77)
  - Z Magazine, 1992 -- 1993; MS014.001.077.00014; The Institute for Social and Cultural Communcations (Box 77)
  - Z Papers, 1992; MS014.001.077.00015; The Institute for Social and Cultural Communcations (Box 77)
  - Zenger's News Magazine, 2008 -- 2009; MS014.001.077.00016; Zenger's (Box 77)
  - 1 in 10, 1995; MS014.001.077.00017; Boston Phoenix (Box 77)
  - 2nd Amendment Reporter, 1977; MS014.001.077.00018; Second Amendment Foundation (Box 77)
  - 50 Years is Enough, 2007; MS014.001.077.00019; US Network for Global Economic Justice (Box 77)
- Chip Berlet research files, 1923 -- 2011; 1970 -- 2011; MS014.002; 57 Linear Feet 54 record cartons, 2 letter sized document boxes, and 1 oversized box.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific materials are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  The Chip Berlet research files series contains materials collected and created by PRA analyst Chip Berlet, spanning from the creation of the Midwest Research Institute in 1981 to approximately 2011. This series contains direct mail, fliers, and publications from conservative groups across the United States, and research materials about these groups. These materials deal with topics including women's rights, abortion, sexual consent, sexual assault, physical assault, immigration law, racism, the Klu Klux Klan, the Nazi Party, white supremacy, religion, LGBTQ rights, conversion therapy, and more. Additionally, this series contains several boxes of materials relating to political activist Lyndon LaRouche and the organizations he was associated with including the National Democratic Policy Committee.
  Content Warning
  Materials in this series contain images and language that are racist, homophobic, and sexist, as well as images that depict graphic sexual content, graphic violence, and dead human bodies and fetal remains. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  Appraisal
  89 empty folders, one box of phone message slips, monetary donations, blank stationery, manuals for office equipment, office invoices, and two boxes of major newspapers and publications held by other institutions were deaccessioned from this series. These materials were out of scope or duplicative.
  This series is organized into six sub-series: Newspaper clippings; Direct mail; Organizational records; Publications; Research and subject files; and Speeches and conferences. The Direct mail sub-series is arranged in alphabetical order. The Clippings, Organizational records, Publications, Research and subject files, and Speeches and conferences sub-series are arranged in received order.
  - Newspaper clippings, 1940 -- 2002; MS014.005396; 5 Linear Feet 4 record cartons, 1 oversized box.
    This sub-series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
    This sub-series contains newspapers and newspaper clippings related to right-wing organizations. Many of the newspapers and newspaper clippings in this sub-series were published in the United States; there are a few international publications. Topics addressed in this sub-series include the activities of right-wing organizations, Nazism, white supremacy, militias, and individual right-wing figures.
    - Newspaper clippings and research files, 1940 -- 1990; MS014.005397; 1 Box(es) (Box 1)
      75 years from date of creation.
    - Newspaper clippings, 1969 -- 2000; MS014.005398; 1 Box(es) (Box 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1984 -- 2002; MS014.005399; 1 Box(es) (Box 3)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1970 -- 1991; MS014.005400; 1 Box(es) (Box 4)
    - Oversized newspaper clippings, 1978 -- 1995; MS014.005401; 1 Box(es) (Box 5)
  - Direct mail, 1978 -- 2011; MS014.005402; 12 Linear Feet 12 record cartons.
    - Direct mail A, 1980 -- 2009; MS014.005403; 1 Box(es) (Box 6)
    - Direct mail A-C, 1978 -- 2009; MS014.005404; 1 Box(es) (Box 7)
    - Direct mail C, 1982 -- 2009; MS014.005405; 1 Box(es) (Box 8)
    - Direct mail C-D, 1983 -- 2008; MS014.005406; 1 Box(es) (Box 9)
    - Direct mail D-E, 1987 -- 2009; MS014.005407; 1 Box(es) (Box 10)
    - Direct mail F-H, 1982 -- 2009; MS014.005408; 1 Box(es) (Box 11)
    - Direct mail H-L, 1982 -- 2009; MS014.005409; 1 Box(es) (Box 12)
    - Direct mail L-N, 1984 -- 2009; MS014.005410; 1 Box(es) (Box 13)
    - Direct mail N-O, 1981 -- 2009; MS014.005411; 1 Box(es) (Box 14)
    - Direct mail P-R, 1981 -- 2009; MS014.005412; 1 Box(es) (Box 15)
    - Direct mail R-U, 1982 -- 2009; MS014.005413; 1 Box(es) (Box 16)
    - Direct mail U-Z, 1982 -- 2011; MS014.005414; 1 Box(es) (Box 17)
  - Organizational records, 1970 -- 1994; MS014.005415; 1 Linear Feet 1 record carton.
    The materials in this sub-series relate to the creation and organization of Political Research Associates including correspondence, office publications, and administrative records.
    - Organizational records, 1970 -- 1994; MS014.005416; 1 Box(es) (Box 18)
  - Publications, 1972 -- 2004; MS014.005417; 1 Linear Feet 1 record carton.
    The materials in this sub-series focus on the publications created and distributed by Political Research Associates.
    - PRA publications, 1972 -- 2004; MS014.005418; 1 Box(es) (Box 19)
  - Research and subject files, 1923 -- 2010; MS014.005419; 35 Linear Feet 33 record cartons and 2 letter sized document boxes.